powermen.com 2016-06-26

# Powermen.com | Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it readily available and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on PowerMen.com. On some pages, you can order videos, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are your name, address and e-mail address. We also collect your date of birth for adult verifacation purposes.

## The Way We Use Information

We NEVER sell or allow access to our mailing list or any other personal information to any external company. We might update our customers by e-mail or by mail with new products. If you do not wish to be on our e-mail list, please send us an e-mail at webmaster@powermen.com from your e-mail address including the word "remove" in the subject box. If you do not wish to be on our postal mailing list, please fax us at (212) 924-3529, or mail to:

Silvertree Media  
101 West 23rd Street  
#700  
New York, NY 10011 

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We Invite You to Review Our Billing Partner's Policy

MuscleHunks.com is in partnership with ccBill.com.  
We invite you to review their Privacy Statement.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending us an e-mail at data@powermen.com.

We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (212) 242-6000, or fax us at (212) 924-3529. You may also e-mail us at data@powermen.com,or write us at the address shown above.
